Armed with the truth
The Game Changers is a documentary film directed by Louie Psihoyos.
From the UFC Octagon in Las Vegas and the anthropology lab at Dartmouth, to a strongman gym in Berlin and the bushlands of Zimbabwe, the world is introduced to elite
athletes, special ops soldiers, visionary scientists, cultural icons, and everyday heroes—each on a mission to create a seismic shift in the way we eat and live.
Self (voice), played by James Wilks.
Self, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Self, played by Patrik Baboumian.
Self, played by Scott Jurek.
Self, played by Dotsie Bausch.
Self, played by Tia Blanco.
The Game Changers is a 2018 American documentary film about
vegan athletes who follow plant-based diets.
The film explores themes of sports, diet, food, environmental, fitness.